A Guide to the Shelton-Winn-Oliver Family Papers, 1764-1965
Library of Virginia
- Oversize (Box 37)
  - The Soldier's Visitor, vol. 1, no. 10, (May 1864) (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Stewart's Ride Around McClellan (Chickahominy Raid) Map (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Wallpaper Sample (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - "Western Carolinian" (Salisbury, NC), vol. 111, no. 156, (3 June 1823) (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Will of Walter Coles, 1815 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Woodson vs. Chick admr. (Box 37, Folder 22)